Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series VI. Publications
  - Chapter Newsletters, 1995-2002
    - Seattle/Bellevue, WA (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Seymour, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Shasta, CA (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Sonora/Motherlode (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - South Bend (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - South Coast (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Southcentral Alaska (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Indiana (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Southern Crescent (GA) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Southern Maine (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Southern Oregon/Northern California (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Southwest Michigan (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Southwestern Connecticut (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Spokane, WA (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Stanislaus (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - State College, PA (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - State Council, NM (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Stockton/San Joaquin, CA (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Summit County, CO (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Syracuse (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Toledo (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Traverse City Area, MI (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Treasure Valley (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Tri-Cities (Bay City, Midland, Saginaw) (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Tucson (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Tulsa, 1997-2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Ventura County (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Victoria, TX (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Waco (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Washington, DC (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Washington State (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Western Colorado (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Williamstown/Berkshire (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Winston-Salem, NC (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Wichita (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Yakima, WA (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Yolo County, CA (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - York, PA (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Youngstown (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Billings (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Fredericksburg/Rappahannock, VA (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Fremont (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Lexington Park-St. Mary's (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Portland, OR (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Winchester-Lower Shenandoah Valley (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Austin, TX, 2005-2009 (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Bryan/College Station (Box 65, Folder 60)
    - Greater Chicago, 2006-2008 (Box 65, Folder 61)
    - Findlay (Box 65, Folder 62)
    - Houston, TX (Box 65, Folder 63)
    - Lake County (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln, NE, 2002-2008 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - North Iowa (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - St. Joseph/Berrien County (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Seymour, 1998-2009 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Shreveport, LA (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Tulsa, OK, 2005-2009 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Northern Illinois (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Wooster (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Lima (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Fort Wayne, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Fort Worth, 1999, 2008-2009 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Oakland/East Bay (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Henderson County (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Kensington, NH (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Norwalk, CT (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Plymouth Concord, NH (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - South Atlantic Region (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Tressler (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Chautauqua, NY (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Triangle Chapter, NC (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Boston, MA (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Fayetteville (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Flat Rock/Hendersonville (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Forest Grove (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Fort Lauderdale (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Skagit (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Detroit, 2005-2009 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Erie (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Estes Park (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Eugene/Springfield (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Bakersfield (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Baltimore (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - North Bay, CA (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - North Olympic Peninsula (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Northern NJ (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Northern NM/Santa Fe (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - O'Ahu (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Evergreen/Mountain Area (CO) (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Fairbanks (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Fargo/Moorhead, 1995-1999, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- Series VII. Project Open Mind
  - Information packet, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - POM Campaign Manual, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ads: Shepardson, Stern and Kaminsky, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ads: TV Buys - Media buy info, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Ads: St. Louis, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ads: St. Paul/Minneapolis, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ads: Seattle, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - POM Consultants, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Consultant contracts: national, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Consultant contracts: Atlanta, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Consultant contracts: Houston, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Consultant contracts: St. Paul/Minneapolis, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Consultant contracts: Seattle, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Consultant contracts: Tulsa, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Kamber Group Proposal, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - EDK Associates: Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - EDK Associates, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    "P-FLAG's Project Open Mind: Messages for a Public Education Campaign Report", 3 bound copies: draft, confidential, unmarked
  - EDK Associates: "Fact vs. Belief: Shaping the Conflict Over Gay and Lesbian Equality", 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - EDK Associates: Interim Project Open Mind National Report, 19 Feb., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Endorsement information packets, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - National endorsements, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Atlanta endorsements, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Houston endorsements, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - St. Louis endorsements, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - St. Paul/Minneapolis endorsements, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Seattle endorsements, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Tulsa endorsements, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - POM Hand-Outs, Fact Sheets, Q and A, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fundraising: National, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fundraising: Atlanta, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Fundraising: Houston, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Fundraising: St. Louis, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Fundraising: St. Paul/Minneapolis, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Fundraising: Seattle, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Fundraising: Tulsa, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Financials - Plan, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - National financials, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - St. Paul/Minneapolis financials, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Seattle financials, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - POM Strategic Planning
    - Management Team (Steering Committee), 1994, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Concerns, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - National, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Daily Reports, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Weekly Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Interim Report, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - National Report 14 March 1997, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Atlanta, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Houston, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - St. Louis, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - St. Paul/Minneapolis, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Seattle, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Tulsa, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - POM Presentation Handbook, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - POM Trainings on Site
    - Training Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Atlanta, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Houston, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - St. Paul/Minneapolis, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Seattle, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Tulsa, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Leadership Training Institute 1994, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Pride I and II post May 1994 [ = POM Training - Seattle], 19941995 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - POM Chapters Requests - West, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - POM Potential Next Cities, 1995, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - POM Miscellaneous, 1991-1996 (Box 19, Folder 64-65)
  - Advertising/fundraising proposal, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - POM misc., 1990-1994 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - POM misc., 1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - POM proposals, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Howard Gilman Foundation, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Major donor development, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Donor correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - POM misc., 1995 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Harris Wofford, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - EDK Associates misc., 1993 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - POM Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Project Open Mind--Funding, 1994-1996 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Project Open Mind, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Project Open Mind--Legal, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Project Open Mind Press Release, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Project Open Mind--KY, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Project Open Mind Regional Training Conference, Tidewater, VA, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - POM: Henderson, KY Training, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Project Open Mind, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Project Open Mind materials, including POM Campaign Manual, media coverage, publicity materials, research, 1995-1998 (Box 57, Folder 2-70)
- Series VIII. Conferences
  - P-FLAG National Conventions
    - Conventions: Guidelines, 10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Materials, miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Invitations and program, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Evaluations of Seattle, Washington, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Convention in New Orleans, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Convention in New Orleans, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Convention in San Francisco, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Detroit, MI, 20-23 October, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Reaching Out into the 90's," Anaheim, CA, 12-14 October, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
    - "Celebrating the Jewels in Our Crown," Charlotte, NC, 11-14 October, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
    - "Love in Action - Joy in Diversity," Seattle, WA, 4-7 September, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
    - "Celebrating Family New Orleans Style," New Orleans, LA, 3-6 September, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10-12)
    - "Bridges to Equality," San Francisco, CA, 2-5 September, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 13-16)
    - Digital Queers Computer Skills Basic Training, San Francisco, CA, 2-5 September, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Indianapolis, IN: "summary of evaluations" only - other conference materials not sent by P-FLAG, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - "Love Takes Action: Building a Nation of Equality," Washington, D.C., 11-14 October- program, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Leadership Training Institute: "Youth and Education," Washington, D.C., 11 October, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
    - Orlando, FL, 11-14 September: program; letter declining invitation sent to President Clinton, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Conference Articles, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Conference Audiotapes, 1982-1996 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      order forms, orders, miscellaneous information related to audiotapes of P-FLAG National Conventions and Leadership Training Institutes
      Audiotapes contained in Series IX
    - Misc. convention materials, 1981-1984 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Misc. convention materials, 1985-1988 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Misc. convention materials/booklets, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - 9th Annual Convention program, Anaheim, CA, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - 10th Annual Convention program, Charlotte, NC, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - 10th Annual Convention program, Charlotte, NC, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Misc. convention materials, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Convention planning materials, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Misc. convention materials, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Seattle convention materials, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Potential presenters, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Leadership Training Day budget, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Leadership Training Institute manual, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - New Orleans convention materials, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Convention planning materials, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - New Orleans presenters, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Regional Directors' Leadership Training Institute proposal kit, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - LTI budget, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Advocacy training, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Leadership Training Day, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - LTI proposal final draft, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - LTI "Know Your Enemy" pamphlet, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - New Orleans Conference program, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Convention queries, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - San Francisco convention materials, including program, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - LTI materials, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Indy '95 workshop logistics, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Indy '95 workshop contacts, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Indy '95 planning materials, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Indy '95 evaluations, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Advocates for Youth 15th Anniversary Conference, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Future workshop ideas, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - DC '96 Convention planning timeline, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - DC '96 planning, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - DC '96 workshop planning, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - DC '96 program team plans, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Geo's workshop, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - DC '96 roundtables, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - DC '96 workshops, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - DC '96 plans, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - DC '96 planning materials, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Lambda Conference, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Orlando conference materials, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Misc. conference planning materials re: location, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Misc. conference planning materials re: location, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Leadership Training Institute materials, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Conference speaker negotiations, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - "Youth and Education Leadership Training Institute" conference '96, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Misc. conference materials, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Misc. conference materials, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Convention 1982--Los Angeles, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - Conference--New York City, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 61)
    - Convention 1984--Denver, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 62)
    - Convention 1985, Atlanta, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 63)
    - Convention 1986--Portland, OR, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 64)
    - Convention 1987--Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 49, Folder 65)
    - Convention 1988--Chicago, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - Bridges to Equality--Convention 1994, San Francisco, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 67)
    - Convention: Indy 95--Indianapolis, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 68)
    - Convention Staff Book, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 69)
    - 15th Conference, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 70)
    - Conference 1996--Washington, D.C.--official welcome letters, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 71)
    - 15th International Conference, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - Conference 1996--Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 49, Folder 73)
    - National Conference 1996 Booklet, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 74)
    - Convention/Conference Publications, 1996-2002 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - Conference, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - Leadership Training Institute (at National Convention): Religion, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 77)
    - National Conference 2000--Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 49, Folder 78)
    - National Conference 2002 Workshop Proposals, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - National Conference 2004--Salt Lake City, UT, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 80)
    - First International Convention 1982--Los Angeles, CA, August 5 - 8, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - 1984 Convention Program - Denver, CO, September 28 - 30, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - 1985 Convention Program - Atlanta, GA - "What Will the Neighbors Say?", October 25 - 28, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - 1986 Convention Program - Portland, OR - "RAP On Homophobia A Search For Understanding", September 19 - 21, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - 1987 Commemorative Banquet Program and Convention Program - Washington, DC - "Equality for Our Gay Children - Let's Make It Happen", October 23 - 26 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - 1988 Commemorative Banquet Program - Chicago, IL - "United in Love - We are Family", October 7 - 10, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - 1989 International Convention - Novi, MI - "Listening, Learning, Loving", October 20 - 23, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      Conference Program, Worship Service Pamphlet, Daily Schedule Booklet, correspondence, etc.
    - 1990 International Convention - Anaheim, CA - "Reaching Out Into the 90s", October 12 - 14, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      Banquet Program, Free Hug Coupon, Federation Board Ribbon, Hyatt Regency Brochure, Presenter Ribbon, Convention Program, etc.
    - 1992 Commemorative Program - Seattle, WA - "Love in Action: Joy in Diversity" and registration packet, September 4 - 7, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - 1994 Convention Program - San Francisco, CA - "Bridges to Equality" - 13th Annual International Convention, September 2 - 5, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - 1995 Convention Program - Indianapolis, Indiana - "Educating Families Toward Love and Acceptance", September 29 - October 1, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - 1996 Convention Program - Washington, DC - "Building A Nation of Equality", October 11 - 14, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - 1997 Convention Program - Orlando, FL - "The PFLAG Family Adventure: Making the World a Safer Place", September 11 - 14, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - 2002 Convention Program - Columbus, OH - "Family Voices for Equality", September 27 - 29, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - 2004 Convention Program - Salt Lake City, UT- "Celebrating 30 Years of Support, Education and Advocacy", October 22 - 24, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - 2007 Convention Program and other conference materials - Mclean, VA - "Family Voices Moving Equality Forward", October 11 - 14, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - 1997 Final Conference Reports, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - P-FLAG Regional Conferences
    - "A Matter of Justice and Compassion: Addressing the Needs of Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgendered Youth", P-FLAG Wichita, Kansas Chapter, October 28, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 24-26)
    - "Our Family Values" P-FLAG Mid-Atlantic Conference, 20 April, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Northeast Regional Conference planning materials, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Pacific Northwest "New Frontiers for the 90's" brochure, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Mid-Atlantic Tri-Regional Conference materials, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Northeast conference: "Celebrate Youth", 1992 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Misc. regional/state conference materials, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - Central Region Conference (Madison, WI), 2003 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - Northern CA Regional Meeting, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - "We are Family Standing Tall and Growing," 1989 Annual Dinner of New York City PFLAG, November 12, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 56)
    - "We are Family Standing Tall and Growing," 1993 Annual Dinner of New York City PFLAG, November 6, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 57)
    - Northeast Regional Strategic Meeting Advertisement, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Transcending Boundaries and Northeast PFLAG Conference 2006 - Worcester, MA, October 27 - 29, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Georgia Chapters of PFLAG Present: Rodeo: A Conference on LGBT Equality, April 1, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - PFLAG Super-Regional Conference 2008 - Gulf Region and South Altantic Region, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Series IX. Audiocassettes and Videocassettes
  - 1982 P-FLAG National Convention, Los Angeles, 6-7 August
    - Politics in the Gay/Lesbian Movement (Box 8, Folder 82-A)
      Morris Kight; Dorr Legg; Duncan Donovan
    - Lesbians in the Women's Movement (Box 8, Folder 82-B)
      Ivy Bottini; Amy Ross
    - Public Relations (Box 8, Folder 82-C)
      Linda Valentino; Dick Ashworth; Joe Bernstein; Duncan Donovan
    - Gays Coming Out to Family and Friends (Box 8, Folder 82-D)
      Agnes McLaughlin; Max and Mildred Warsaw; Norma Coates
    - Legislation Affective Lesbians and Gays (Box 8, Folder 82-E)
      Attorneys Susan McGrievy and Thomas Coleman
    - Speaker's Bureau (Box 8, Folder 82-F)
      Amy and Dick Ashworth; Adele and Larry Starr
    - Bulk Mailing and Packet Assembly (Box 8, Folder 82-G)
      Lyle Henry and Agnes McLaughlin
    - How to Facilitate a Rap Group (Box 8, Folder 82-H)
      Gerry Shields; Edith Ogolsky; Pat Paddock; Mildred Warsaw
    - How to Handle a P-FLAG Hotline (Box 8, Folder 82-I)
      Arleen Nelson, MSW; Adele Starr
    - Organizational Challenges (Box 8, Folder 82-J)
      Dick Ashworth, Esq; Bea Bernstein; Al Gordon, Esq; Larry Starr, CPA
    - Alcoholism in the Gay Community (Box 8, Folder 82-K)
      Max Schneider, MD; Chris Aloperi; Ray Fruge
    - Counseling Spouses and Friends (Box 8, Folder 82-L)
      Arleen Nelson, MSW, moderator
    - Religion: Educating about Gays (Box 8, Folder 82-M)
      Tom Sauerman; Harlan Adams
    - Gay/Lesbian Couples: Legal Problems and Estate Planning (Box 8, Folder 82-N)
      Al Gordon, Esq
    - Gay/Lesbian Literature and History (Box 8, Folder 82-O)
      Jim Kepner, Archivist; Dick Follett, PhD
    - Gay/Lesbian Health Concerns (Box 8, Folder 82-P)
      Jim Lipsett, MD; Neil Schram, MD
    - An Arrest in the Family - missing (Box 8, Folder 82-Q)
      Duncan Donovan; Al Gordon, Esq; Arnold and Rita Stone
    - Sharing Ideas and Experiences (Box 8, Folder 82-R)
      Pat Paddock, moderator
    - The Gay/Lesbian Adolescent (Box 8, Folder 82-S)
      Teresa DeCrescenzo, MSW; Alan Malyon, PhD
    - Lesbian Visibility in Professional Careers (Box 8, Folder 82-T)
      Kay Loveland, Esq; Amy Ross
    - Awards Banquet and Entertainment (Box 8, Folder 82-U)
      Leroy Dysart; Los Angeles Gay Men's Chorus, Great American Yankee Freedom Band
  - 1983 P-FLAG National Convention, New York, 7-10 October
    - Counseling Parents: Handling newcomers, telephone counseling, distinguishing gay and non-gay issues, referral to professional help (Box 8, Folder 83-A)
      Jeanne Manford; Paulette Goodman
    - Coming Out: To Parents, to family, to friends, neighbors and co-workers (Box 8, Folder 83-B)
      Anne Harris; Madelyn Mignatti
    - Running Discussion Groups: Smaller groups, facilitators, summaries to larger groups, keeping control, leading topics, attention to newcomers, follow-up, participation of lesbians and gay men (Box 8, Folder 83-C)
      Elinor Lewallen; Dick Ashworth
    - Materials for Education of Parents: programs, guest speaker topics, resources, books, articles, reports, pamphlets, audio-visual, film (Box 8, Folder 83-D)
      Barbara Gittings
    - Fundraising: within the parents group, fundraising events, grants, support from lesbian/gay community (Box 8, Folder 83-E)
      David Rothenberg; Dr. Tom Sauerman
    - Psychological Approach to Homophobia: Homophobia is a social disease, taking the offensive against prejudice, non-gay therapists, anti-gay violence, pedophilia, transvestism - missing (Box 8, Folder 83-F)
      George Weinberg, PhD; Ann Greene
    - Speaking: soliciting speaking engagements, gearing presentation to audience, recruiting and training speakers (Box 8, Folder 83-G)
      Amy Ashworth; Arthur Siegel; Bob Benov
    - Lesbian and Gay Adolescents: social concerns, isolation, runaways, role models legal concerns, public policies, youth organizations, high school programs, manifestations, stereotypes (Box 8, Folder 83-H)
      Emery Hetrick; Ken Redmond
    - Media and Public Relations: getting coverage, how to present views to the media, advertising articles, newsletters, referrals from professions, self-help groups (Box 8, Folder 83-I)
      Ethan Geto; Michele de Milly